Guide to the Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives Printed Ephemera Collection on Individuals PE.030
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- R, 1910-2005; 3.75 Linear Feet in 3 record cartons, 1 manuscript box, and 1 oversize shared box
  - Reed, John, 1887-1920, 1919 (Box 23)
  - Reich, Wilhelm, 1897-1957, 1971 (Box 23)
  - Reinstein, Boris, undated (Box 23)
  - Reitman, Ben L. (Ben Lewis), 1879-1942 (Box 23)
  - Relgis, Eugen, 1964 (Box 23)
  - Remington, William Walter, b. 1917, undated (Box 23)
  - Reston, James, 1909-1995, 1965 (Box 23)
  - Reuther, Walter, 1907-1970, 1933, undated (Box 23, Box 35, Folder 25)
  - Revels, Hiram Rhoades, 1827?-1901, 1960, undated (Box 23, Box 35, Folder 26)
  - Rezler, Julius, 1959 (Box 23)
  - Ribicoff, Abraham, undated (Box 23)
  - Rich, J. C. (Jacob C.), 1947 (Box 23)
  - Richardson, Beulah, 1962 (Box 23)
  - Richardson, Thomas, 1963 (Box 23)
  - Richberg, Donald R. (Donald Randall), 1881-1960, 1929 (Box 23)
  - Richler, Mordecai, 1931-2001, 1992 (Box 23)
  - Ries, W. F., undated (Box 23)
  - Riesman, David, 1942 (Box 23)
  - Riis, Mary Phillips, 1964 (Box 23)
  - Ringsdorf, Anna Maley, circa 1915 (Box 23)
  - Ripley, William Zebina, 1867-1941, undated (Box 23)
  - Rius, 1976 (Box 23)
  - Rivera, Dennis, 1990 (Box 23)
  - Rivera, Diego, 1886-1957, 1932 (Box 23)
  - Rivera, Oscar Garcia, undated (Box 23)
  - Rizzi, Bruno, 1966 (Box 23)
  - Rizzo, Frank, undated (Box 23)
  - Robel, Gene, undated (Box 23)
  - Roberts, Archibald E., 1968 (Box 23)
  - Robertson, James, 1963 (Box 23)
  - Robeson, Eslanda Goode, 1949 (Box 23)
  - Robeson, Paul, 1898-1976 I, 1947-1998 (Box 24, Box 35, Folder 27)
  - Robeson, Paul, 1898-1976 II, 1947 (Box 24)
  - Robeson, Paul, 1898-1976 III, 1947 (Box 24)
  - Robeson, Paul, 1898-1976 IV, 1947 (Box 24)
  - Robeson, Paul, 1898-1976 V, 1947 (Box 24)
  - Robeson, Paul, 1898-1976 VI, 1947 (Box 24)
  - Robinson, Cleveland, 1914-1995, 1966 (Box 24)
  - Robinson, Earl, 1910-1991, 1989 (Box 24)
  - Robinson, William J., Dr., 1933 (Box 24)
  - Rochester, Anna, 1966 (Box 24)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. (Nelson Aldrich), 1908-1979, undated (Box 24, Box 35, Folder 28)
  - Rocker, Fermin, 1945 (Box 24, Box Shared Tamiment 006, Folder 6)
  - Rocker, Rudolf, 1873-1958 I, 1922 (Box 24)
  - Rocker, Rudolf, 1873-1958 II, 1922 (Box 24)
  - Rocker, Rudolf, 1873-1958 III, 1922 (Box 24)
  - Rodney, Lester, 1911-, 2005 (Box 24)
  - Roebling, Emily, 1953 (Box 24)
  - Rogers, Walter and Elizabeth (Elizabeth S. Cousins Rogers) I, 1969 (Box 24)
  - Rogers, Walter and Elizabeth (Elizabeth S. Cousins Rogers) II, 1969 (Box 24)
  - Rogoff, Hillel, undated (Box 24)
  - Rojas, Don, 1986 (Box 24)
  - Rolland, Hugo, 1973 (Box 24)
  - Romualdi, Serafino, 1947 (Box 24)
  - Rooney, John J., 1944 (Box 24)
  - Roosevelt, Eleanor, 1884-1962, 1946 (Box 24)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin D. (Franklin Delano), 1882-1945 I, 1936 (Box 24)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin D. (Franklin Delano), 1914-1988 II, 1936 (Box 24)
  - Roosevelt, James, 1907-1991, 1966 (Box 24)
  - Roosevelt, Theodore, 1858-1919, undated (Box 24)
  - Root, Robert Cromwell, b. 1858, 1915 (Box 24)
  - Rorty, James, 1890-1973, 1950 (Box 24)
  - Rose, Alex, b. 1898, 1976 (Box 24)
  - Rosen, Moe, 1965 (Box 24)
  - Rosenberg, Ethel, 1915-1953 and Rosenberg, Julius, 1918-1953 I, 1951 (Box 24)
  - Rosenberg, Ethel, 1915-1953 and Rosenberg, Julius, 1918-1953 II, 1951 (Box 24)
  - Rosenberg, Ethel, 1915-1953 and Rosenberg, Julius, 1918-1953 III, 1951 (Box 25)
  - Rosenberg, Ethel, 1915-1953 and Rosenberg, Julius, 1918-1953 IV, 1951 (Box 25)
  - Rosenberg, Ethel, 1915-1953 and Rosenberg, Julius, 1918-1953 V, 1951 (Box 25)
  - Rosenberg, Isaac, 1890-1918, 1960 (Box 25)
  - Rosenfeld, Kurt, 1943 (Box 25)
  - Rosenfeld, Morris, 1862-1923, 1962 (Box 25)
  - Rosmer, Alfred, 1936 (Box 25)
  - Rotenberg, Sol, 1974 (Box 25)
  - Roth, Henry, 1995 (Box 25)
  - Rothbard, Murray Newton, 1926-1995, undated (Box 25)
  - Roy, M. N. (Manabendra Nath), 1887-1954, 1985 (Box 25)
  - Rubel, Maximillian, 1967 (Box 25)
  - Rubinow, I. M. (Isaac Max), 1875-1936, 1913 (Box 25)
  - Ruby, Jack, 1964 (Box 25)
  - Rugg, Harold, 1942 (Box 25)
  - Rushmore, Howard, undated (Box 25)
  - Rusby, George L., undated (Box 25)
  - Russell, Bertrand, 1872-1970 I, 1951 (Box 25)
  - Russell, Bertrand, 1872-1970 II, 1951 (Box 25)
  - Russell, Charles Edward, 1860-1941, 1910 (Box 25)
  - Russell, Maud, 1893-1989, 1950 (Box 25)
  - Russell, Phil, 1982 (Box 25)
  - Russo, Michael, 1952 (Box 25)
  - Russo, Pasquale, 1923 (Box 25)
  - Rustin, Bayard, 1912-1987 I, 1963 (Box 25)
  - Rustin, Bayard, 1912-1987 II, 1963 (Box 25)
  - Ruthenberg, Charles E. (Charles Emil), 1882-1927, 1918 (Box 25)
  - Rutherford, Judge, undated (Box 25)
  - Ryan, John A., 1912 (Box 25)
  - Rybakov, I., 1917 (Box 25)
- S, 1883-2005; 6.25 Linear Feet in 5 record cartons, 2 manuscript boxes, and 2 shared boxes
  - Sacher, Harry, 1949 (Box 25)
  - Sacks, Benjamin, 1903-, 1936 (Box 25)
  - Sadoul, J., undated (Box 25)
  - Saillant, Louis, 1974 (Box 25)
  - Salvemini, Gaetano, 1873-1957, 1926 (Box 25)
  - Sakisaka, Itsurō, 1897-, 1961 (Box 25)
  - Salit, Cathy Rose, undated (Box 25)
  - Samuels, Gertrude, 1964 (Box 25)
  - Sandberg, Karl F. M., 1912 (Box 25)
  - Sanders, Bernie, undated (Box 25, Box 35, Folder 29)
  - Sanger, Margaret, 1920 (Box 25)
  - Sanger, William, 1915 (Box 25)
  - Sanial, L. (Lucien), b. 1836, 1927 (Box 25)
  - Santen, Sal, 1961 (Box 25)
  - Santo, John, 1941 (Box 25)
  - Saposs, David J. (David Joseph), 1886-1968, 1929 (Box 25)
  - Sarkar, Benoy Kumar, 1887-1949, 1918 (Box 25)
  - Sasson, Abraham, undated (Box 25)
  - Sattler, Otto, 1950 (Box 25)
  - Saxe, Susan, 1975-1977 (Box 25, Box 35, Folder 30, Box Shared Tamiment 187, Folder 13)
  - Sayre, Francis Bowes, 1915-, 1964 (Box 25)
  - Scales, Junius, undated (Box 25)
  - Schachner, Eugene, 1937 (Box 25)
  - Schaffle, A., 1890 (Box 25)
  - Schappes, Morris U. (Morris Urman), 1907- I, 1947 (Box 25)
  - Schappes, Morris U. (Morris Urman), 1907- II, 1947 (Box 25)
  - Scherman, Harry, 1938 (Box 25)
  - Schiff, Philip, 1937 (Box 25)
  - Schikowski, John, 1920 (Box 26)
  - Schlamme, Martha, 1985 (Box 26)
  - Schlesinger, Arthur M. (Arthur Meier), 1917-2007, 1947 (Box 26)
  - Schluter, Hermann, 1907 (Box 26)
  - Schneiderman, Rose, 1882-, 1991 (Box 26)
  - Schneiderman, William, 1941 (Box 26)
  - Schneir, Walter, 1972-1991 (Box 35, Folder 31)
  - Schoenfeld, Myer, 1896 (Box 26)
  - Schrader, Frederick Franklin, undated (Box 26)
  - Schrecker, Ellen, undated (Box 26)
  - Schreiner, Olive, 1972 (Box 26)
  - Schroeder, Theodore, 1864-1953, 1910 (Box 26)
  - Schuman, Frederick L. (Frederick Lewis), 1904-1981, 1958 (Box 26)
  - Schurz, Carl, undated (Box 26)
  - Schwartz, Delmore, 1913-1966 (Box 26)
  - Schwartz, Pinkhos, 1963 (Box 26)
  - Schwarz, Fred, 1913-, 1962 (Box 26)
  - Schwarzenfeld, Alex, undated (Box 26)
  - Schwarzschild, Leopold, 1891-1950, 1949 (Box 26)
  - Schwarzschild, Stephen, 1956 (Box 26)
  - Schwimmer, Rosika, 1877-1948, undated (Box 26)
  - Scott, Howard, 1932 (Box 26)
  - Seager, Henry R. (Henry Rogers), 1870-1930, 1913 (Box 26)
  - Seale, Bobby, undated (Box 26)
  - Secklar, Alvena, 1954 (Box 26)
  - Sedov, Lev Lvovich, undated (Box 26)
  - Seeger, Pete, 1919-, 1950 (Box 26)
  - Segal, Ben, undated (Box 26)
  - Segal, Benjamin D., undated (Box 26)
  - Segal, Edith, 1902-, 1964 (Box 26)
  - Segal, Louis, 1964 (Box 26)
  - Segal, Martin E., 1951 (Box 26)
  - Seger, Gerhart Heinrich, 1896-, undated (Box 26)
  - Seghers, Anna, undated (Box 26)
  - Seibman, Joel, 1935 (Box 26)
  - Seidel, Emil, 2002 (Box 26)
  - Seidman, Bert, 1975 (Box 26)
  - Seidman, Carol, 1970 (Box 26)
  - Seignobos, Charles, 1918 (Box 26)
  - Seldes, George, 1890-1995, 1923 (Box 26)
  - Seldes, Gilbert, 1932 (Box 26)
  - Selekman, Benjamin M. (Benjamin Morris), 1893-1962 (Box 26)
  - Seligman, Edwin, undated (Box 26)
  - Seller, Maxine S., 1987 (Box 26)
  - Sellins, Fannie, 1872-1919, 1989 (Box 26)
  - Seltzer, David, 1904-, undated (Box 26)
  - Semard, Pierre, undated (Box 26)
  - Sender, Toni, 1888-1964 (Box 26)
  - Senior, Clarence Ollson, 1903-1974, 1950 (Box 26)
  - Serge, Victor, 1890-1947, 1940 (Box 26)
  - Serrette, Dennis, 1987 (Box 26)
  - Service, John S., 1957 (Box 26)
  - Shachtman, Max, 1903-1972 I, 1963 (Box 26)
  - Shachtman, Max, 1903-1972 II (Box 26)
  - Shachtman, Yetta Barsh, 1996 (Box 26)
  - Shahn, Ben, 2001 (Box 26)
  - Shanker, Albert, 1997 (Box 26)
  - Shapiro, Samuel, 1960 (Box 26)
  - Sharansky, Anatoly, 1880-2020 (Box 35, Folder 32)
  - Sharp, Clarence, 1981 (Box 26)
  - Sharts, Joseph W. (Joseph William), b. 1875, 1915 (Box 26)
  - Shaw, Bernard, 1856-1950, 1921 (Box 26)
  - Shaw, Elisabeth Ross, 1920 (Box 26)
  - Shaw, Nena Beth, 1989 (Box 26)
  - Sheehan, Frank, 1966 (Box 26)
  - Sheehy, Maurice S. (Maurice Stephen), b. 1898, undated (Box 26)
  - Sheil, Bernard J. (Bernard James), 1888- 1969, 1943 (Box 26)
  - Shelley, Percy Bysshe, 1792-1822, 1883 (Box 26)
  - Sherman, Alfred Kund, 1985 (Box 27)
  - Sherman, Joseph, undated (Box 27)
  - Sherover, Max, b. 1889, 1937 (Box 27)
  - Shevchenko, Taras, undated (Box 27)
  - Shibley, George E., undated (Box 27)
  - Shields, Art, 1888-, 1939 (Box 27)
  - Shier, William Restelle, undated (Box 27)
  - Shils, Edward, 1910-1995, 1958 (Box 27)
  - Shimmons, Earl W., undated (Box 27)
  - Shinner, E. G., 1955 (Box 27)
  - Shiplacoff, Abraham I., 1936 (Box 27)
  - Shipley, Maynard, 1872-1934, 1919 (Box 27)
  - Shipley, Ruth, 1944 (Box 27)
  - Shister, Joseph, 1945 (Box 27)
  - Sholem Aleichem, 1859-1916, 1964 (Box 27)
  - Sholokhov, Mikhail, undated (Box 27)
  - Sholomovich, A. C., 1926 (Box 27)
  - Shotwell, James Thomson, 1874-1965 (Box 27)
  - Shub, Anatole, 1969 (Box 27)
  - Shuster, George Nauman, 1894-, undated (Box 27)
  - Shutz, Moses, 1968 (Box 27)
  - Shuvaloff, Count, 1905 (Box 27)
  - Shvernik, N. M. (Nikolai Mikhailovich), 1888-1970, 1943 (Box 27)
  - Sibley, Mulford Quickert, 1964 (Box 27)
  - Sichinskii, M., undated (Box 27)
  - Sieverman, Frank A., undated (Box 27)
  - Silberman, Charles E., 1925-, 1963 (Box 27)
  - Silkwood, Karen, 1946-1974, 1978-1994 (Box 27, Box 35, Folder 33)
  - Silone, Ignazio, 1900-1978, 1936 (Box 27)
  - Silver, Adolf, 1927 (Box 27)
  - Silvey, Ted F., 1955 (Box 27)
  - Simons, A. M. (Algie Martin), 1870-1950, undated (Box 27)
  - Simons, Mary Wood, d. 1984, undated (Box 27)
  - Sinclair, John (Committee to Free), undated (Box 27)
  - Sinclair, Mary Craig, 1961 (Box 27)
  - Sinclair, Upton, 1878-1968, 1926 (Box 27)
  - Siqueiros, David Alfaro, 1962 (Box 27)
  - Sirovich, William I., 1930 (Box 27)
  - Skeels, Jack, 1961 (Box 27)
  - Slasky, Rudolf, 1951 (Box 27)
  - Slayton, J. W. (John W.), circa 1910 (Box 27)
  - Slitcher, Sumner H. (Sumner Huber), 1892-1959, 1942 (Box 27)
  - Slobodin, Henry L., undated (Box 27)
  - Slochower, Harry, 1900-, 1956 (Box 27)
  - Smedley, Agnes, 1892-1950, 1945 (Box 27)
  - Smiley, James B., undated (Box 27)
  - Smith, Billy Dean, 1948-, undated (Box 27)
  - Smith, Edwin S., 1976 (Box 27)
  - Smith, Gerald L.K., 1945 (Box 27)
  - Smith, Hilda Worthington, 1935 (Box 27)
  - Smith, Katharine, 1980 (Box 27)
  - Smith, Lillian Eugenia, 1897-1966, 1942 (Box 27)
  - Smith, Louise Pettibone, 1887-, 1962 (Box 27, Box 35, Folder 34)
  - Smith, R. L. T. (Robert L. T.), 1961 (Box 27)
  - Smith, Rennie, 1929 (Box 27)
  - Smith, Walker C., 1927 (Box 27)
  - Smyth, William H., 1920 (Box 27)
  - Sobell, Helen, 1956 (Box 27)
  - Sobell, Martin I, undated (Box 27)
  - Sobell, Martin II, 1953 (Box 27)
  - Sobell, Martin III, 1960 (Box 27)
  - Sobell, Martin IV: Committees to Free/ Secure Justice for, 1966 (Box 27)
  - Solarz, Steve, 1973 (Box 27)
  - Sollmann, Wilhelm, 1881-1951, 1936 (Box 28)
  - Solneman, K. H. Z., 1975 (Box 28)
  - Solomon, Charles, 1920 (Box 28)
  - Solomon, Sidney, 2005 (Box 28)
  - Solomon, Usher, undated (Box 28)
  - Solzhenitsyn, Alexander, 1975 (Box 28)
  - Sombart, Werner, 1863-1941, 1909 (Box 28)
  - Sorin, Vladimir, undated (Box 28)
  - Sostre, Martin, 1971 (Box 28)
  - Sozzi, Gastone, undated (Box 28)
  - Spalding, F. S., 1909 (Box 28)
  - Spargo, John, 1876-1966, 1898 (Box 28)
  - Spartakus, undated (Box 28)
  - Spectator/Spektator, undated (Box 28)
  - Spector, Maurice, 1968 (Box 28)
  - Spellman, Francis, 1889-1967, 1961 (Box 28)
  - Spencer, Fanny Bixby, undated (Box 28)
  - Spencer, Harold, undated (Box 28)
  - Speyer, Ed, 1946 (Box 28)
  - Spiess, George Jr./Goldstein, David, 1913 (Box 28)
  - Spillane, John J., undated (Box 28)
  - Spira, Henry, 1998 (Box 28)
  - Spock, Benjamin, 1903-1998, 1984, undated (Box 28, Box 35, Folder 35)
  - Sprading, Charles T., undated (Box 28)
  - Squires, Richard, Maj., 1952 (Box 28)
  - St. John, Francis R., 1964 (Box 28)
  - St. John, Lucy, 1969 (Box 28)
  - Stace, W. T., undated (Box 28)
  - Stakhanov, A. G. (Aleksandr Grigoryevich), 1939 (Box 28)
  - Stalin, Joseph, 1879-1953, 1929-1988 (Box 28, Box 35, Folder 36, Box Shared Tamiment 186, Folder 10)
  - Stallard, H. H., undated (Box 28)
  - Stamm, Thomas, 1979 (Box 28)
  - Stampfer, Friedrich, undated (Box 28)
  - Stanton, Elizabeth Cady, 1815-1902, undated (Box 28)
  - Stanton, William J., undated (Box 28)
  - Starobin, Joseph R. (Joseph Robert), 1913-1976 (Box 28)
  - Starobin, Sol, 1936 (Box 28)
  - Starr, Mark, 1894- I, 1938 (Box 28)
  - Starr, Mark, 1894- II, 1948 (Box 28)
  - Stavis, Barrie, 1982 (Box 28)
  - Steele, Jack, 1914-1980, undated (Box 28)
  - Steels, Jean, 1935 (Box 28)
  - Stein, Emanuel, 1908-1985, 1950 (Box 28)
  - Stein, Leon, 1912-, 1990 (Box 28)
  - Steinem, Gloria, 1972 (Box 28)
  - Steinmetz, Charles Proteus, 1865-1923 (Box 28)
  - Stephens, Jessie, 1912 (Box 28)
  - Sternberg, Harry, 1947 (Box 28)
  - Stetin, Sol, 1982 (Box 28)
  - Stevens, Thaddeus, 1942 (Box 28, Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Stevenson, Adlai E. (Adlai Ewing), 1900-1965 (Box 28)
  - Still, J. W., 1965 (Box 28)
  - Stimson, Henry L. (Henry Lewis), 1867-1950, 1947 (Box 28)
  - Stirner, Max, 1967 (Box 28)
  - Stokes, Anson Phelps, 1874-1958 (Box 28)
  - Stokes, Elizabeth Dilling, 1894-1966 (Box 28)
  - Stokes, James Graham Phelps, 1872-1960 (Box 28)
  - Stokes, Rose Pastor, 1879-1933, undated (Box 28)
  - Stolberg, Benjamin, 1891-1951, 1938 (Box 28)
  - Stone, I. F. (Isidor Feinstein), 1907-1989, 1941 (Box 28)
  - Stone, N. I. (Nahum Isaac), b. 1873, 1913 (Box 28)
  - Story, Russell McCullouch, 1927 (Box 28)
  - Strachey, John, 1901-1963, undated (Box 28)
  - Streit, Clarence K., undated (Box 28)
  - Strobell, G. H., undated (Box 28)
  - Strong, Anna Louise, 1885-1970, 1930 (Box 28)
  - Stulberg, Louis, 1901-1977, 1966 (Box 28)
  - Sturmthal, Adolf Fox, 1950 (Box 28)
  - Sturzo, Don Luigi, 1944 (Box 28)
  - Suall, Irwin, 1961 (Box 28)
  - Suhl, Yuri, undated (Box 28)
  - Sullivan, J. W. (James William), 1848-, 1896 (Box 28)
  - Sullivan, Thomas R., undated (Box 28)
  - Sun Yat-Sen, 1912 (Box 28)
  - Sunday, Billy, undated (Box 28)
  - Suzman, Helen, 1966 (Box 28)
  - Swados, Harvey, 1957 (Box 29)
  - Swann, Edward, undated (Box 29)
  - Sweeney, John (Box 29)
  - Sweezy, Paul M. (Paul Marlor), 1910-2004, 1958 (Box 29)
  - Swift, John, 1952 (Box 29)
  - Swinton, John, 1892 (Box 29)
  - Sylvis, William H., 1828-1869, 1949 (Box 29)
  - Szántó, Béla, 1920 (Box 29)
- T, 1902-2008; 2.75 Linear Feet in 2 record cartons, 1 manuscript box, and 1 oversize shared box
  - Tabert, Martin, 1923 (Box 29)
  - Taddei, Ezio, 1895-1956, undated (Box 29)
  - Taft, Henry W. (Henry Waters), 1859-1945, 1921 (Box 29)
  - Taft, Philip, 1902- I, 1937 (Box 29)
  - Taft, Philip, 1902- II, 1942 (Box 29)
  - Taft, Robert Alphonso, 1952 (Box 29)
  - Talbot, Thomas Wilson, 1975 (Box 29)
  - Talen, William, 2008 (Box 29)
  - Talentire, Norman H., 1953 (Box 29)
  - Talmadge, I. D. W., 1948 (Box 29)
  - Tamiment Library -- Staff, 1992 (Box 29)
  - Tannenbaum, Frank, 1919 (Box 29)
  - Taylor, Glen H., 1964 (Box 29)
  - Taylor, Harold, undated (Box 29)
  - Taylor, Harold W., 1946 (Box 29)
  - Taylor, Maurice, undated (Box 29)
  - Taylor, Recy, 1945 (Box 29)
  - Taylor, Sam, 1938 (Box 29)
  - Taylor, Terry, 1993 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Tead, Ordway, 1891-1973, 1918 (Box 29)
  - Teller, Ludwig, 1965 (Box 29)
  - Tenney, Jack B., 1953 (Box 29)
  - Terzani, Athos, 1965 (Box 29)
  - Thalheimer, August, 1931 (Box 29)
  - Thälmann, Ernst, 1886-1944, 1940 (Box 29)
  - Thatcher, Margaret, undated (Box 29)
  - Thomas, Frances Violet Stewart, undated (Box 29)
  - Thomas, Julius A., 1945 (Box 29)
  - Thomas, Norman, 1884-1968 I, 1918 (Box 29)
  - Thomas, Norman, 1884-1968 II, 1918 (Box 29)
  - Thomas, Norman, 1884-1968 III, 1918 (Box 29)
  - Thomas, Norman, 1884-1968 IV, 1964 (Box 29)
  - Thomas, Norman, 1884-1968 V, undated (Box 29)
  - Thomas, Norman, 1884-1968 VI (Committees to Elect), 1928-1948 (Box 29)
  - Thompson, Carl D., 1913 (Box 29)
  - Thompson, Dorothy, 1893-1961 (Box 29)
  - Thompson, E. P. (Edward Palmer), 1924-, 1993 (Box 29)
  - Thompson, Robert, 1915-, 1944 (Box 29)
  - Thompson, William B., undated (Box 29)
  - Thoreau, Henry David, 1817-1862, 1965 (Box 29)
  - Thorez, Maurice, undated (Box 29)
  - Thorne, Ahrne, 1985 (Box 29)
  - Thrane, Marcus Møller, 1817-1890, 1936 (Box 29)
  - Thurton, Rod, 2000 (Box 29)
  - Tichenor, George, 1959 (Box 29)
  - Till, Emmett, 1941-1955, 1955-1956 (Box 30, Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Timasheff, Nicholas S. (Nicholas Sergeyevitch), 1886-1970, undated (Box 30)
  - Timpson, Ann Burlak, 1983 (Box 30)
  - Tippett, Tom, 1929 (Box 30)
  - Tito, Josip Broz, 1892-1980, 1955 (Box 30)
  - Titus, Herman F., 1919 (Box 30)
  - Tobias, Abraham Joel, 1913-, 1935 (Box 30)
  - Tobler, Max, 1920 (Box 30)
  - Tobocman, Seth, undated (Box 30)
  - Todd, Jane H., 1966 (Box 30)
  - Togliatti, Palmiro, 1893-1964, 1956 (Box 30)
  - Tolischus, Otto D. (Otto David), 1890-, 1940 (Box 30)
  - Tolstoy, Leo, graf, 1828-1910, undated (Box 30, Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Tompkins, James, undated (Box 30)
  - Toner, Jerome L. (Jerome Lorraine), b. 1899, 1957 (Box 30)
  - Tornquist, Elizabeth, 1961 (Box 30)
  - Toscanini, Arturo, 1867-1957, 1943 (Box 30)
  - Townsend, Willard S., 1945 (Box 30)
  - Toynbee, Arnold, 1961 (Box 30)
  - Trachtenberg, Alexander, 1884-1966, 1939 (Box 30)
  - Trachtman, Arnold, 1981 (Box 30)
  - Tratino, Tommy, 1975 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Traubel, Horace, 1902 (Box 30)
  - Travis, Robert C., undated (Box 30)
  - Trepper, Léopold, 1904-, 1972 (Box 30)
  - Tresca, Carlo, 1879-1943, 1925- (Box 30)
  - Trotsky, Leon, 1879-1940 I, 1934-1940 (Box 30, Box 36, Folder 6, Box Shared Tamiment 184, Folder 28)
  - Trotsky, Leon, 1879-1940 II, 1934 (Box 30)
  - Trotsky, Leon, 1879-1940 III, 1934 (Box 30)
  - Trotsky, Leon, 1879-1940 IV, 1934 (Box 30)
  - Trostsky, Lev: Assassination, 1972 (Box 30)
  - Trumbo, Dalton, 1905-1976, 1970 (Box 30)
  - Tsereteli, I. G. (Irakli Giorgis), 1881-1959 (Box 30)
  - Tsiang, H. T., undated (Box 30)
  - Tubman, Harriet, 1942 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Tucker, Benjamin Ricketson, 1854-1939, undated (Box 30)
  - Tucker, Irwin St. John, 1886-1982, undated (Box 30)
  - Turitz, Morris, 1957 (Box 30)
  - Turner, Nat, 1800?-1831, undated (Box 30)
  - Tuvim, Abraham, 1958 (Box 30)
  - Tuvim, Joseph, undated (Box 30)
  - Tyler, Gary, 1976 (Box 30)
  - Tyler, Gus, 1961 (Box 30)
  - Tyner, Jarvis, undated (Box 30)
  - Tyrrell, John P., 1927 (Box 30)
  - Tyson, James L., 1940 (Box 30)
- U, 1911-1970; 1.5 Linear Feet in 1 record carton and 1 manuscript box
  - Ulbricht, Walter, 1893-1973, 1946 (Box 30)
  - Ulman, Lloyd, 1961 (Box 30)
  - Ulmer, Melville J. (Melville Jack), 1911-, 1959 (Box 30)
  - Unger, Henrik, 1921 (Box 30)
  - Uphaus, Willard E. (Willard Edwin), 1890-1983, 1970, undated (Box 30, Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Usher, Robert J., 1911 (Box 30)
- V, 1908-2004; 2.5 Linear Feet in 2 record cartons and 1 manuscript box
  - Vail, Charles H., undated (Box 30)
  - Valenti, Girolamo I, 1952 (Box 30)
  - Valenti, Girolamo II, 1952 (Box 30)
  - Valenti, Jack, 1999 (Box 31)
  - Valtin, Jan, 1904-1951, undated (Box 31)
  - Van Arkel, Gerhard P., undated (Box 31)
  - Van Arsdale, Harry, 1905-1986, 1950- (Box 31)
  - Van den Haag, Ernest, 1953 (Box 31)
  - Van Kleeck, Mary, 1908 (Box 31)
  - Van Riper, Ellis F., 1957 (Box 31)
  - Van Vechten, Carl, 1880-1964 (Box 31)
  - Vanzetti, Bartolomeo, 1888-1927, 1958 (Box 31)
  - Vaptsarov, Nikola, 1948 (Box 31)
  - Varga, Eugen, 1879-1964, 1960 (Box 31)
  - Vassails, Gerard, 1950 (Box 31)
  - Veblen, Thorstein, 1857-1929, undated (Box 31)
  - Venanzi, Flavio, 1921 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Verinder, Frederick, undated (Box 31)
  - Veritas, undated (Box 31)
  - Verwoerd, Hendrik Frensch, 1901-1966 (Box 31)
  - Viereck, Peter, 1916-2006, 1949 (Box 31)
  - Villard, Oswald Garrison, 1872-1949, 1920 (Box 31)
  - Vishniak, Mark, 1942 (Box 31)
  - Viveiros, Camilo, 2004 (Box 31)
  - Vladeck, B. (Baruch), 1886-1938, 1911, 1939 (Box 31)
  - Vladeck, Judith P., 1994 (Box 31)
  - Vladeck, William, 1958 (Box 31)
  - Vogel, Virgil A., 1994 (Box 31)
  - Volkov, Esteban (Box 31)
  - Vorse, Mary Heaton, 1874-1966 (Box 31)
  - Voynich, E. L. (Ethel Lillian), 1864-1960, 1959 (Box 31)
- W, 1902-2005; 3.75 Linear Feet in 3 record cartons, 1 manuscript box, and 1 oversize shared box
  - Wagenknecht, Alfred, 1943 (Box 31)
  - Wagner, Otto, 1908 (Box 31)
  - Wagner, Robert F. (Robert Ferdinand), 1910-1991, undated (Box 31)
  - Waksman, Selman A. (Selman Abraham), 1888-1973, 1958 (Box 31)
  - Wald, George, 1969 (Box 31)
  - Wald, Lillian D., 1867-1940, undated (Box 31)
  - Walden, Daniel, 1960 (Box 31)
  - Waldman, Louis, b. 1892, 1920 (Box 31)
  - Walker, Edwin A. (Edwin Anderson), 1909-, 1964 (Box 31)
  - Walker, Edwin C., 1908 (Box 31)
  - Walker, James L., undated (Box 31)
  - Wallace, George C. (George Corley), 1919-1998, 1963-1968 (Box 31)
  - Wallace, Henry A. (Henry Agard), 1888-1965, 1936-1945 (Box 31, Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Wallace, Henry A. (Henry Agard), 1888-1965, 1946-1975 (Box 31)
  - Wallace, Henry A. (Henry Agard), 1888-1965, undated (Box 31)
  - Waller, Odell, 1940 (Box 31)
  - Walling, Anna Strunsky, 1879-, 1964 (Box 31)
  - Walling, William English, 1877-1936, 1917 (Box 31)
  - Walsh, J. Raymond, undated (Box 31)
  - Walter, Francis E. (Francis Eugene), 1894-1963, 1960 (Box 31)
  - Walsh, Frank, 1978 (Box 31)
  - Wanamaker, John, 1918 (Box 31)
  - Wanhope, Joseph, undated (Box 31)
  - Wanhope, Joshua, undated (Box 31)
  - Wanrow, Yvonne, undated (Box 31)
  - Wansley, Thomas Carlton, 1963 (Box 31)
  - Warbasse, James Peter, 1866-1957, 1934 (Box 31)
  - Warburg, James P., 1965 (Box 31)
  - Ward, Harry Frederick, 1873-1966, 1923 (Box 31)
  - Ward, Paul W., 1947 (Box 31)
  - Ward, Roosevelt, Jr. (Committee to Defend), 1951 (Box 31)
  - Ware, Harold M. (Box 31)
  - Waring, J. Waters, 1950 (Box 31)
  - Warren, A. P., 1935 (Box 31)
  - Warren, Earl, 1955 (Box 31)
  - Warren, Fred D., 1872 or 3-1959, 1911 (Box 31)
  - Warren, Susan, 1955 (Box 31)
  - Washington, George, 1732-1799, 1963 (Box 31)
  - Washington, Samuel, undated (Box 31)
  - Waters, Mary-Alice, undated (Box 32)
  - Wayland, J. A. (Julius Augustus), 1854-1912 (Box 32)
  - Weaver, Robert C. (Robert Clifton), 1907-1997, 1941 (Box 32)
  - Webb, Beatrice Potter, 1858-1943, 1947 (Box 32)
  - Webb, Marilyn Salzman, 1968 (Box 32)
  - Webb, Sidney, 1859-1947, 1912 (Box 32)
  - Webber, Charles C., 1931 (Box 32)
  - Webster, W. L., 1918 (Box 32)
  - Wechsler, James A., 1963 (Box 32)
  - Weeks, Rufus W., undated (Box 32)
  - Weinberg, Morris, 1964 (Box 32)
  - Weiner, Norbert, 1894-1964 (Box 32)
  - Weinryb, Bernard D. (Bernard Dov), 1900-, 1946 (Box 32)
  - Weinstein, Charles, d. 1959 (Box 32)
  - Weinstein, James, 1926-, 2005 (Box 32)
  - Weinstein, Murray, 1958 (Box 32)
  - Weinstein, Sam, undated (Box 32)
  - Weinstone, William W. (William Wolf), 1897-1985 (Box 32)
  - Weir, Stan, 1983 (Box 32)
  - Weisberg, Julius, 1938 (Box 32)
  - Weisbord, Albert, 1900-, 1977 (Box 32)